[{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664685368,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":88015,"timeElapsed":257599},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664709568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":24198,"timeElapsed":281799},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664752384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":42814,"timeElapsed":324615},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664785129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":32743,"timeElapsed":357360},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664815624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":30493,"timeElapsed":387855},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664874005,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":58379,"timeElapsed":446236},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664915736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":41728,"timeElapsed":487967},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664941944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":26206,"timeElapsed":514175},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735664954464,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":12519,"timeElapsed":526695},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665029968,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":72167,"timeElapsed":602199},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665063400,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":33430,"timeElapsed":635631},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665109696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":46295,"timeElapsed":681927},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665131744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":22046,"timeElapsed":703975},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665135896,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4151,"timeElapsed":708127},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665190168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":54271,"timeElapsed":762399},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665205856,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":15687,"timeElapsed":778087},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665256904,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":51047,"timeElapsed":829135},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665269008,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"77","question":"If someone offered to financially support a comfortable life for you and your loved ones, for the rest of your life, with the only stipulation that they would eat your body after you die, would you take the offer? Why or why not?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":12102,"timeElapsed":841239},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665299481,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":28943,"timeElapsed":871711},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665312760,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":13279,"timeElapsed":884991},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665320448,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":7687,"timeElapsed":892679},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665325208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4759,"timeElapsed":897439},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665328624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3415,"timeElapsed":900855},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665341776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":13151,"timeElapsed":914007},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665346568,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":4790,"timeElapsed":918799},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665352208,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5639,"timeElapsed":924439},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665355776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"70","question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3567,"timeElapsed":928007},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665364824,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"If you could meet any person living or dead, who would it be and why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":9047,"timeElapsed":937055},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665388480,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":22439,"timeElapsed":960711},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665393344,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4863,"timeElapsed":965575},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665405232,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":11887,"timeElapsed":977463},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665416265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":11032,"timeElapsed":988496},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665421120,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4854,"timeElapsed":993351},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665433313,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":12191,"timeElapsed":1005544},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665437513,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":4199,"timeElapsed":1009744},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665442465,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4951,"timeElapsed":1014696},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665448984,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"176","question":"What is your strategy for eating a really messy taco?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":6518,"timeElapsed":1021215},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665468272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":17935,"timeElapsed":1040503},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665472264,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3991,"timeElapsed":1044495},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665477656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":5391,"timeElapsed":1049887},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665485635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":7975,"timeElapsed":1057866},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665490360,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4723,"timeElapsed":1062591},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665512988,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":22627,"timeElapsed":1085219},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665517712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4723,"timeElapsed":1089943},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665521736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4023,"timeElapsed":1093967},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665530488,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"178","question":"What school subject were you best at? Worst at?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8751,"timeElapsed":1102719},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665577729,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":45495,"timeElapsed":1149959},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665590328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":12599,"timeElapsed":1162559},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665600272,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":9942,"timeElapsed":1172503},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665608288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":8015,"timeElapsed":1180519},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665612720,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":4431,"timeElapsed":1184951},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665633648,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":20927,"timeElapsed":1205879},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665646176,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":12527,"timeElapsed":1218407},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665655073,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":8896,"timeElapsed":1227304},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665662384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":7310,"timeElapsed":1234615},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665697456,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":33350,"timeElapsed":1269687},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665702712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":5255,"timeElapsed":1274943},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665715216,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":12503,"timeElapsed":1287447},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665722832,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":7614,"timeElapsed":1295063},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665727592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":4759,"timeElapsed":1299823},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665738664,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":11071,"timeElapsed":1310895},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665743473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":4807,"timeElapsed":1315704},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665747369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3895,"timeElapsed":1319600},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665755929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"99","question":"Under what circumstances do you think you could kill someone, if any?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":8559,"timeElapsed":1328159},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665789592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":32327,"timeElapsed":1361823},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665796944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":7351,"timeElapsed":1369175},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665808184,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":11239,"timeElapsed":1380415},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665813000,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":4815,"timeElapsed":1385231},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665819873,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6871,"timeElapsed":1392104},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665833553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":13679,"timeElapsed":1405784},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665843393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":9838,"timeElapsed":1415623},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665847217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":3824,"timeElapsed":1419448},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665851473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4254,"timeElapsed":1423703},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665871961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"171","question":"Have you ever tried to learn a TikTok dance? How did it go?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":20487,"timeElapsed":1444192},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665885953,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":12247,"timeElapsed":1458183},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665890601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":4647,"timeElapsed":1462831},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665895880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":5279,"timeElapsed":1468111},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665899825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":3943,"timeElapsed":1472056},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665905200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":5374,"timeElapsed":1477431},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665908961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3759,"timeElapsed":1481192},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665926585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":17623,"timeElapsed":1498816},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665930129,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3543,"timeElapsed":1502360},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665936601,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"175","question":"Do you have a default pizza order? What is it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":6471,"timeElapsed":1508832},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665952553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":14647,"timeElapsed":1524784},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665956529,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":3975,"timeElapsed":1528759},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665960617,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":4087,"timeElapsed":1532848},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665972265,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":11646,"timeElapsed":1544496},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665976273,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":4007,"timeElapsed":1548504},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735665996233,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":19959,"timeElapsed":1568464},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666001785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":5551,"timeElapsed":1574016},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666012337,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":10551,"timeElapsed":1584568},{"subjectID":"v4b2pjpejc","prolificID":"676eec5a51ca999bb2023bad","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6774216521e7421aea49c3a9","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735666018401,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"88","question":"If you could cook just one dish to express who you are to someone, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":6063,"timeElapsed":1590632}]